Hello
worldareanEnglish
snowcountryisapart
ofJapanthateslots
andlotsofsnowIdone accessible
manytripsacrossto
Japangoingbybikeby
trainbyfairiesbyany
formof
transportationIcan
findthistimeIwanted
tovisitpartsofJapan
snowcountrythat
could onlybebycarsoI
setouttoexplore
Yamagatawiththegoal
ofreachingthesecret
Japanesetownwiththe
highestsnowfallon
thistripAsusual,I'm
bringingalongmypart
producerandfulltime
sisterinlaw.In
addition,wehavea
specialguest,AO
sister.Andincase
you'renotmakingthe
connection,that's
correct,mywifeis
comingalongforthe
ride.Westartherein
Nicoanddoyou
rememberthisplace
wasbaronland?Well,
westartedbuilding
andit'sgnabeamini
hoteljustthreerooms
openinginmaybeJune
of2025.thisyear.But
anyways,thisvideois
notaboutbehindme.We
gnaleavefromhereand
leave the Nicoareand
gotoYag. So, let's
[music]
is
tickets. You can ride on the bigger
and bigger the
small
life.
Except though. It's
bigger than I thought
[music]
.  Ithoughtitwastwo
butthat'sHakuen
whichis1800yenwhich
islikeIdon'tknowor
somethingforthisone
ride.Ionlyboughtsix
ticketssoIcanonly
ridethisonetwiceorI
couldrideoneofthe
smartsafewmore
times.SoweseewhatI
[Music]
do.Beautiful
NowifthinkingI'm
drunkfilmthisthen
youdbewrongthatbe
you'rethinkingabout
itturnsoutforsetmy
pockettotherighteSo
it'sslikeaboat.I
apologize.AsI
suspected,theexpert
coursewasmorelikea
bluethanablackrun.
Eggplant, eggplant beef.  It's a cow with an eggplant belly.
[Music]
Yeah.  How much was it? 12. 1200 yen.
Well, yeah.  The meat is tender.
This costs 1000 yen.  1000 yen.  Oh, the
meat is tender.  Like this, yeah
.  It's simply delicious.   I
simply said it was delicious.  Yeah.  Yeah.   The
meat is tender, though.  Well, it's spicy but delicious.
Yeah.  This is the only option.
Yeah.
[Music]
Yeah.  The meat is tender, isn't it?  Yeah.   with
lunchadonedeal
I exchange
my tickets for
the gondola ride backup
to the top this is
small uffed up may
see the windows always
get all marked up so having
protection is not bad
thing I
[music]
think OK which one where
?
Oh, that might be good.
I like pink, but do you think this pink suits me? I can't really tell because my
face is so toned.
[Music]
Oh, I might not have recorded it.   Oh no.  You're
kidding, right? I didn't take it.
Wait, it didn't
come off? I've been doing it like this the whole time.
[Music]
Littletownwepassed
byandwepassedbyit
becauseIdecidedto
usethelocaltofree
roadsversusgoingon
thetohighway.The
highwaywouldhave
beensmootherand
fasterbutforaroad
tripwhatwouldbethe funinthatasluck
wouldhaveitwithmy
droneintheairandat
theofthecartheto
limitedexpressrtrwe
onlastyearmag
[Music]
Isupposenowbeasgood
timeasanytothrowupa
mapandshowyou
exactly whereweare
going.Westartedoff
inNicowhichis
inhuntermountainand
thencrossingover
intoFukushima
onlastyearandIdida
tripthroughthisvery
areabytrain,but
beingabletogetthe
droneupintheair
givesyousucha
different
perspective.Wedid
havesnowtiresonthe
carwhichare called
studedinafewdays,
themainroadswere
very clear.Although
therehadbeenlarge
dumpsofsnowearlier
andyoucouldseethe
[Music]
accumulation.Ithink
thesnowwillbetwice
Or three times as deep
in Yamagata, certain
areas, but
I mentioned this in a
past video, but these red and white poles are used to mark the roads in the winter as the snow comp to make it unclear where the lines are. As we were winding our way through little mountain villages and towns, I spotted some familiar landmarks and realized I had some unfinished business. This was my chance to get my revenge, and I know that strong but in Japanese was used more like when you take a bath but
could
revenge
time we found our way back at
what is this I forgot
Yugami Onsen Yugami Onsen I came again Yes I came again
[music]
[applause] I told you to stop
.  Stop it
.  It's almost too hot.
Oh, you're right.   That's
dangerous, it's really
dangerous.  And you can even paint it.  socks.
Oh, so you did that?  That
was close, hey, that was close.  I don't really like that.  This is what I did.  That's amazing.
These shoes are amazing, they're actually my dad's.  Okay, let's eat.  Ah, that feels good.  No way.  My foot, please.  Look, this part is blue.  Oh,
no.  Because you'll fall over.  I don't like it when there's just one
person there.   The
other room was so bad I took a picture of my feet in Intonite
.
Isn't it a belly/leg fetish?  And also, yes, me
.  And it's blue!
[Music] That
's amazing.   Isn't
this related to something else? I didn't see anything on the news about them making a request to the mountain winds in Iwate.
[Music]
While peacefully
driving between prists in
snow-covered
fields, I spotted pulsing red lights off
the distance. I saw one, another, and the flow to stop. By the time I got the drone up the air, a couple of fire
department vehicles had already passed us by. It turns out all these vehicles coming in from the country to help with wildfest. As night was falling, I drove through the area of ​​Fukushima and into the southern tip of Yamaga. Climbing up the mountains, the snow continued to get deeper and deeper. For those of you that know
Japanese geogray, you
might guess what we decided to eat. I've never done anything like this before.  thank you for your
hard work.  It's delicious.
It is famous for being one of the
top three or four
brands in Japan, so of course we had to judge for
ours. Let's go for it! It's
delicious.  Hmm.  Wow, that's great.
[Music]
Yes.
Okay.  Oh, you're right.  amazing.
Yeah.  Yeah.   It's
soft.  Yeah.  I'll be going now.   Can I
really drink this? Yakiniku (Japanese BBQ).
Oh, I ordered this.  Oh, then, here's the appetizer.  I ate my meal without putting this down.  Yeah.  That's true
.  About the same as Doreci.   It's
delicious, isn't it?
This is my meal.   This is
beef sushi made with Yonezawa beef.  I want to eat it.
amazing.  They cost 770 yen each.   I'm going to get
meat sushi.
I'm half.  Oh
, what are you doing?  We have to do it all in one go.  Yeah.  Let's go all the way at once
.
[Music] It was done
.  Yeah.  The cedar trees are covered in a lot of snow.
[Music]
Can I come in? Oh
, I don't like that
example.  I feel like I'm going to slip.  It's scary, so scary
.  They say there's no one there.  Huh? Nobody's here, so it's
fine.
Me too.  It's snowing heavily
.  How did you get a hand like that
? Wow, that's tough.  Actually, it's cold
.  It's a place with a rich history, isn't it?  There's so much I do
n't know
.  Oh, let's go home now
.  It's always nighttime.   It's
dangerous, isn't it?  amazing.  yes.  We have arrived.
Oh, it's bright.
Yeah.  yes.  Let's go to the hot springs.
yes.  Let's go in.  Let's go in.  yes.
[Music]
PR
take
out
before theste
Ah, this is my favorite Tsuyahime.  What is that? It's
Yamagata's Tsuyahime rice, which is
my favorite rice.  Omori.
[Music]
So what we do is
because we have a car. I
can't ride the train
unfortunately today. So I'm going to send the ladies off on the train from station local train about 45 minutes. We go. This morning's plan is to leave from
Yona. Drop the ladies off at Ak station where
they ride the entire
flower
nage. Then head over to
Yamadato
and the lingering at yamgl
but first we have to get to the train [
music]
station [
[music]
wawa Except they when they were fine, they were just
nervous because then
the next train
wouldn't come for a couple of
hours. On the other hand was bit of a hurry since I wanted to be able to capture the train from the sky. Luckily
, the train
wasn't so quick and I was able to get drone up in [music]
time. And this is where
paying close
attention to the
footage
pays. Now if you can sp
you see
[music]
me trust me
There. Come
you be seeing now.
[Music]
Right in hand and there
you
[Music]
H
next Nishidai Yes
.  45
Yes.  thank you.  yes.  And then there's snow shoveling.
Yeah, I was that
could ride the little
flow train. Like many
rural train lines, the
volume of passengers
is high.
[music] I've actually
traveled to quite a few different places by train.   I
agree.  I've traveled all over Japan, and I really enjoy train travel, so I've been to many places
.  I'm going around.
yes.  There are a lot of anime-style things like this lately, aren't there?   I
agree.
What is this anime collaboration? They're doing an anime collaboration.
Apparently, this female anime character visits ramen shops all over the country, and although I haven't watched all of them, I got Tsuyahime rice.  It's
two per person, right?
So, what are you having for lunch?
Oh, you're really talking a lot.   A
person who eats.  Fuji Home Association.
yes.  Snack time.  It's snack time.
[Music]
Wow.   No way
.  Why would you
deliberately go to a place like this?  This is no time to be shy.
[Music]
If three people are suspicious, it's over, right?   Let's stop
.  Well, that's impossible.  Well, that's impossible.  I'm scared.  Oh, it's me.  No.  Let's stop going to high schools.
[Music] Let's not do that
.  That's wrong.  That's wrong.  Impossible.
Yeah.  It's not that it's impossible, it's just not the same anymore.  That's fine.  I'm going to get in trouble.   It's a
snow attraction.
[Music]
Huh? Why are you going? Why?
Bye.  Oh, hello.   A
sacred place for ramen lovers.
I am the holy land of ramen.
yes.  Okay, let's go into a ramen shop.  I ordered the dangerously miso pork bone ramen.
That's why it's the number one most popular.   He
drank it.
This is amazing.  Great value lunch deals.  I just want to eat a little.  yes.  Someone
ordered this.   I'm counting on you
.  ah.  Yes, yes.
[Music]
Wow, that looks delicious.  Then, what I'd like to say about this is that they had these little affordable side dishes you could order as well, at only 130 in like one US per dish. It felt like a crispy tuna trysome of them out
. So we ordered a lot of ramen bunchof dishes and took turns trying them all out. [Music] How is it? It's delicious, isn't it?  It looks like it would taste good.   Hey, hey,
that's a chat.
Yeah.  hard.
Yeah.  Wobbly.  Yeah.
Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.
[Music]
Yes.  We're going to climb to Yamadera Temple now.
Wow, that's really expensive.   I might quit
halfway through.
amazing.  Let's go.
yes.  This is quite expensive, isn't it?
[Music] It's
really expensive.   No way
.  I don't know.
How do you climb this? It's a
staircase.
Yeah.  My knees hurt.   Your
knees will break.  Complaints are pouring in.
How long will it take? I don't know.
yes.  So, now I'm going to attempt to climb a mountain temple.   It's
Omoshiroyama.  Omoshiroyama is
dangerous.  It's kind of funny.   An
interesting mountain.   It's
not interesting.
But there are quite a lot of people here.
How is it?   It's a
cat.  There's a cat named Chan.  Why are you
here? Is it because it's
warm?
Oh, give me a hug.
Okay, let's just go.
Okay, let's eat when we've climbed up and come down.  As a reward.   A
drink as a reward.
No, I'll really drink it.
yes.  yes.  I can go up a hill.
Oh, well then I'll do my best.  yes.
[Music] It's no
good anymore.  It's just not okay right away.
This is the start.  start.
Mom on the way home.  No, the ground here is pretty rough.  No.
[Music]
Oh, look, look.  Something like this.
Yeah, where's the goal? I
think the highest score I've reached is 6.   Are you
okay? I can go.
Wow, we're already at the stairs.  yes.
yes.   My
ticket changed, so I'm going to climb.  1
hour.  Oh, round trip.  That's an hour round trip.   I
saw a glimmer of hope.
[Music]
360,
640 left.   Really?
But that's quite a lot of panting, isn't it?   I wonder if these
two will get hungry
? Oh, my heart is already pounding.  It's expensive.
[Music]
[Music] It's
loud.  Oh, my
heart's already pounding.
No.  My heart is pounding.
[Music]
No, my heart, my heart is racing.  Oh no, this is bad.  I need to take a
break now, but I'm fine.  Wow, it's already over.   It's
dangerous.  dangerous.  Because it's dangerous.  Seriously, don't do it
.
[Music]
[Applause] Do it
yourself.  That
was 12.  painful.  P-stop it.  Stop it, it hurts.  Stop it.  Don't take it.
[Music]
Huh.
Wow, that's amazing.  Oh, it's beautiful.  It looks like a
mountain valley from a folktale.  Oh, scary, scary, scary, scary.  This is scary.
[Music]
Yeah.
Wait, is this the finish line? Amazing.  That's amazing.  This is really frozen.  This is bad.  terrible.  Ah, heave-ho, heave-ho.  No way.  I don't want to because my face is so ugly.   There are always those who
sprint at the very end.  W-why are you taking me? Here we go, here we go.  What will
come out? It's done.  I climbed it.  I climbed it.  easy.
easy.
yes.  I ended up saying a lot of things, so I'm sorry about that.  It's so beautiful.   it's over
.  It's over.
good.  No, it'll go down next time.
Yeah.  It's incredibly beautiful.  I'm glad I climbed it.   A
resounding success.
Great success.  Okay, then, one, two, three, a
great success!
A little over 1000
steps it was a climb but
nothing to extinguish. It was people in their up with even post at the top that mac climb suto service some of the covered ice are snow
but we all had snow boots on and it was nothing. If that we would have needed spikes for although we did see people attach them to their boots there we received clearing the ice and but because ethereso
muchg What if it gets
cut? I wo
n't go.  I can't go.   Are we still
climbing this?
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait, it's not over yet?
No way.   It looks like the
ramen from earlier is about to come out, but I'll stroke the Buddha
[music].
Mr. Bottle, let's get
used to this for a bit, and my knees too
[music]. My
back hurts.   I also tried
stroking my face all over to see if it would improve.  yes.  Excuse me.  I petted it a little too much.  How far does this go on? Can I really be happy here?  This is the last one.
[Music] That's right
.
Okay.  Excuse me.  I complained about a lot of things, but I did my best and climbed it.   I did it
.  You can be happy.  You can be happy.  I did it.  You can be happy.
Yeah.
This is the goal, right? Yes!  It's over.
What do you want to do next? Well, of course, the next stop is the alcohol section.
yes.  Let's go to the Sakakura section in the liquor department.
yes.  let's go.  let's go.  Let's go carefully so we don't get hurt.
yes.  yes.  yes.  Okay.  And
this is how you do it.
this
.  Oh, I've got it.
[Music] Let's go,
Sakura.  Wow, that's amazing.  This is Gre-chan's favorite.
[Music]
Yeah.
Oh, so what souvenirs should we bring? Just water and sake.
[Music]
Ah, well, it's time for our usual scene again.   Is it
okay to put it in? I'll do it.  Yes
.  Uh, yeah.  Of course it's delicious.  good.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] It's like they're
beginners.  Beginner
[Music] It
stops so easily, doesn't it?  Ah.  oh.  This is easy to drink.  It's all really easy to drink.  It's not too hard.
[Music]
Oh, I like this one.  orange.   I'm
out now.  yes.  I kind of thought the same thing.   It's getting
really hot.  Ah, delicious.
This Ichiro has a slightly different taste.  It's refreshing and easy to drink.   This is the
last one.
Hey, it looks like there's less than before.
[Music]
Not playing.  It won't come out.   It's already
delicious.  This one's delicious too.  The orange-colored cherry blossoms here are delicious.
Let's buy this one.
[Music] I
bought a lot.  I bought a lot.  Take care.
[Music]
For some
glam this would have been a new
experience for all of us while we had seen no trip across Japan we had never been inside the river was located next to a
hotel with that was
free to use and came with and
[Music]
Breakfast go to the
father It's amazing, this is where we
stop.  What will come out? What will come out? Wow.  Oh, that's
cute.  It's warm.
Wow, that's amazing!  Doesn't this feel like a girls' get-together? But there are
two beds here.
Who's sleeping with whom? Oh.
[Music]
Open
featherfe, it's warm
.  This is a girls' get-together with gas fan heaters. I'm
exhausted from showing them off so much.
[Music]
No, I'm tired.  Good work.
But if I don't chill the sake, it will get ruined by the snow
. No, I don't have any sake.
yes.  The break is over.
yes.  thank you for your hard work.  Now, enjoy the rest of the evening.
[Music]
How many bottles are you going to drink?  nice.  What if it gets taken away?  It won't be taken, right?  Maybe I should write something like "Do not pass."  This is a
crime.
Oh, wow, that's amazing!  It's stylish and easy to use, isn't it?
Wow, that's amazing.  This is a BBQ, right? A
BBQ.
What is this? You can
see me sleeping from here.
Oh, this is the toilet.
Ah, I see.
Oh, that's fine.
Oh, that's good.
That's a good idea.
I want to do that too.
Barbecue grill.
oh.  Let's bake it.  I didn't say that here.
[Music]
Yes.  Oh, so we're done after we eat this?
Okay, then you can drink now.
[Music] Is it
good? Can you
see it?
[Music]
What would you like to drink? It's 500 yen a bottle.
Huh, lemon ice cream one.   I'll have
500 lemons.  Okay, I'll go.
yes.  thank you for your hard work.  Good work.  thank you.
[Music]
Ah, it's cold.  Ah,
this is it, this is it.  Huh? It lit up.  this.
Yeah.   I ca
n't quite see this.  Set the
BBQ
grill to maximum and heat it up.  I don't know about one.
I don't understand English at all.
Study.   It must be a really
amazing soy milk hot pot.  It's popular with girls, isn't it?  wait a minute.  Oh, come on over.  Wow, that's amazing.  They look a little too similar.  Oh, look, the meat isn't cooked yet.  Go
[music]
[music] Is that
okay? Go go go.
yes.
Wow, amazing, amazing, amazing.  It's so hot.
Whoa.  The mochi stretches really well.  Yeah.
amazing.
Wait, this isn't cheese, is it?  cheese.
Yeah.  It's mochi, right?  cheese.   Apparently,
this is sake made from a type of rice called Tsuyahime.
Oh, I see.  Because she loves me and the princess.
Yeah.  I bought it just to try it out.   It's
beautiful.  really like.  Wow.
oh.  This is a drink that older men often have.
uncle.  Oh, that's right
.  You're not going there, are you?  Ah
, that's pretty tough.  tight.  strong.
strong.  Oh, slow, slown.  Slow.
nice.  It's okay to take your time.
This
is sake.  cheers.  cheers.
Huh? Yeah.  Huh? I don't know about this
.  Yes, because I really
love it.  Sour, sour, sour.   It tastes
better.   It's
not sweet, is it?
What, it's not sweet?
Well, then try it.  Yeah, it feels kind of
real.
Oh, you're right.  Yeah.   I
like it.  Oh, but it's not Greg.  Yeah.
No, I'm not going
.  This is going to kill you.   mother
.
Yeah.  Hahaha.   Let's do it
.  Let's go to Nokyo tomorrow.  Kure-chan.
Huh, what's Nokyo? Roadside station,
souvenirs, souvenirs, souvenirs.
souvenir.  We still don't have enough souvenirs, do we?   I
bought it.  Win.  I didn't buy it.  So, what kind of
alcohol do you want to buy?
Oh, maybe some mushrooms, or
three kinds of vegetables, or even Yonezawa beef would be good.
Oh, if you're going to
buy us a cow, that would be a fantastic trip.  What a fun trip!  ze ne
.
Yeah.  I'm also caught up in the busyness of every day, but I'm going to take it easy today.  Sanma said something like, "Ah, I see
."  Hurry, hurry, 20.
Yeah.
How was the yakiniku from yesterday?
Yesterday's was better.
[Music]
Oh, are you going to put in such good liquor? Well, anyway, we're pretty low on fluids.  do not have.
Ang
Young.  I'm young.  Are you young?
No, I am.
I
don't. I'm not young. Just try it. I'm old. I can figure that much out.  I
understand that much.  I'm
old, right? That means I'm an old lady, right?
Yes, yes, yes.   I'll do it
.  Explain.
Explanation: When your stomach is full,
Yes.   I'm going to
change the flavor.  Yes.  Please.
Okay.
Well, I'm already full, but it would be a waste not to eat it, wouldn't it?
Food waste is bad, so we should do this with udon noodles too
.  Call me today.
No,
I like spicy food, so put a lot on.  Change of flavor.  Remember the term "flavor change."  If you change the flavor and eat it,
yeah.  I suddenly feel like having carbonara.
[Music] That's
strange.  Yeah.  It's not strange.   I'll straighten
the heat
all the way
up
and the
outcircle we came back Oh, it's okay, stop it, really,
for I'm going to take a hot spring bath, but I wonder if I'll be okay
? I might get sick yeah
.  Let's eat it, it would be a waste not to.
Fluffy.  Let's do our best.  What should I try to eat?
Yes.  Change the flavor.
Buckwheat crepe batter.
[Music]
cream not
real
now I don't know where
the
popcorn
now we cooking now we
popping it's
burning burn what is that burn
Not that great. Oh, you
w
up this is
bucke. Oh, I don't like
those silverdots. The good I think the creammand the silverdot Itadakimasu
.   It's
hot, isn't it?  Chewy.
Yeah.  Yeah.  Write the rice.
Yeah.
Yeah.  Good morning.
good morning.  We just
finished of glaming
and how was it.
Well, the facilities are really nice, and the view is amazing too.  It was my first time camping in a snowy landscape like this, so it was very relaxing and enjoyable.  ood.
Yes, it's okay.  Because it's already prepared, isn't it?
Therewasanownent
justoverthereabouta
few hundred meters
walk.Sothatwas
really nicetohave.Um
butIwouldhave
preferredawoodcabin
instead.Theplastic
smellwaskindof
strong.Andinthein the
morningitwas
actuallyveryveryhot
inthere.LikeIwas
sweatingbecausethe
plastickindof
magnifsowherearewe
goingtonext?Yeah.
Next, we'll go to a roadside station near Tendō Onsen and buy some souvenirs.  Um, I'm going to buy souvenirs for my family.
Okay, let's go.  Let's go.
yes.  yes.  ation.
[Music]
Wow, that's amazing.  Oh, Guru-chan, there's a footbath!
[Music] I'll
buy AcoHeaven.  apple.  Apple juice.  Oh, an apple.  This is amazing, isn't it?   I want to take it home with me
.  Yeah.  My favorite Tsukihime:
yen.  It's a little cheap, isn't it?  So, what did you buy?
This is because my mom likes it.  Hey, hey, Uncle.
Oh, that's the one I drank earlier.  Rice, huh?  I bought a few different kinds.  And this local specialty,
yeah.
Like the Peron team.  Yeah.
Oh, this is for Ako-chan's husband. This dish is rice with a raw egg on top.  Huh? What's that? Was there something like
that? Yeah.
I think I'll buy this jam for now; it looks delicious.
This one, you know, it's jam with butter in it.
Oh, that looks really delicious.
Oh, Tenshi's mom asked me to buy it, so I'll go buy it. It's called Hime Shoyu Mochi.
[Music] That's all
.
[Music]
which is also known as
Japanese chess. They
have an ice new
building dedicated to
highlighting this
fact where you can play a game and also see some
artisans
illustrating the
pieces. It's also because they sell Shogi-related souvenirs that Akobought.
Roadside stations
in general are really
popular as you purchase local goods when you're traveling around Japan, which is why my wife always have to
drop by one wherever we traveled to. I personally picked up a box of Yamagapples for which I got fantastic prizes. [Music] Japan recak [Music] rurnow that the morning shing was out the way we headed into the mountain area. In every new this before the trip, but Zen seems to be popular with tourists. And that's the great thing about these kind of trips for us as we get to discover new places all around Japan. Although as luck would have it not going to the areworld [Music] I really don't want to slip so I'm desperately trying now. Are you
okay?  He's been
arrested.   My
older sister has caught me.   I got a
top score.  I became an actress.
cool.  I like the old lady, but she does
n't slip.   It's just for show
.
yes.   They've
appeared, haven't they?  Yeah.  amazing.  That
[music] is
really dangerous.
Oh, so a rope was strung up from below.
yes.  I'm going to the food review event for men.
yes.  yes.
Shrimp and tomato pet chime.
yes.  I'm having the omelet green curry.  I'll put it in.  The
eggs here are so fluffy.
Really?
Yes.  Buggy to the snow
monsters which are trees blasted by icy winds. What's buggy
you ask? It seems like it's like an ATV that has snow tracks attached that a covered sled behind it. When I booked this thing I had no idea we were actually riding the buggy to the snow monsters
but instead we were taking a regular ski to get there. When getting on and off, put your feet forward. There's a marker there, so
extend your legs like this and extend them.
yes.  And then, um, when you reach the place, put your feet down and get off.
Can I do it?
I'm wearing a backpack.  I'm wearing a backpack.   That's
good, that's good.
yes.  I'm doing it here.  This is what I do.
Wow, that's scary.  I can't do it naturally.  did.
yes.  It's fine to do it later.
yes.  Look at this.  Oh, that's scary, scary, scary.
Wow, wait a minute, just turn it
this way for a bit.  Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, then I'll hold that.  it's okay.   What was
this again? This,
uh, the one in the front, that one, you can
easily find it by taking a walk, I know.  I understand, but are you sure you want to
get off now?
yes.  Okay.  stroll.
Ah, well, that's why I don't like it.   It's okay
.   I tripped and fell right here
, and it was quite a disaster.   Are you
okay? It's really
noisy.  1.
Shut up.  Over here.
Huh? Which one? Which one? This one?
No.  My legs are already... oh, I'm scared, scared, scared.
Huh, isn't that a bit fast? It's fast.
Look, you're saying "aiu" too quickly.  Look.  Oh, that's scary.  Huh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.  Ready, set, go.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Wait.  What is this?
Uh, what is it? No way.  Oh, that's scary.  wait a minute.  Isn't it shaking really hard? No, wait, wait, wait.  This is a bit dangerous.
Why is this shaking?
Yeah, so it's an impact, right? Um, it's really hard to sit down right now, wait a moment.  I was scared.
[Music]
This is unnecessary.  Hey
, it looks like only we are shaking.  Oh, are you done? Lower your feet.  No.  It's absolutely terrifying, terrifying, terrifying.  If you drop it, it's all over.
Yeah.  I wonder if Bull-chan is there?
No, how many years has it been since I last rode this? I
like looking at the back.  Oh, it's finished.  Huh?
What's the matter? No problem.  Isn't the view when you turn around beautiful?
The scenery is amazing.  I can't turn my head.
[Music]
Wow, amazing.  This table looks like Pikachu.
This is a picker. Yes.  If you
come here at night, oh, it really does seem like something might come.   Is
n't a huge hole like the queen's world? I wonder if
everything would fall in if I kicked it with my foot?
Yeah.   I'd kind of like to try it,
but I'd probably get in trouble.
Yeah.  The "Ri" series is also coming to an end.   Oh no.  That's why
it's scary.  You're not very good at it.  Big sister.
No, not me either, I just ran away.  It's scary.  I
stopped it once.  I couldn't get off.
Huh? I stopped it too.
No, no.   It still stands quite a while
.  yes.   Can I
stand up? Oh, that's good.   Honestly, we couldn't have lucked out on a better
day and mountain to see the snow monsters. After I got back home, I was reading reviews of different areas and some people to an hour or two inlines just to see fog-covered snow monsters side stillis apryol [music] [music] Lupe and sunny day
are If you're told that it's not okay to be
a little scared, then it's
over and it's no good.   Look.   Would
n't I get in trouble if I dropped this?
[Music]
Say something nice.  Oh, that's not good right away.  Wow, that's amazing.
So, isn't that enough? It's dangerous.  Where? Like this.  If you do it like this here, it will make a bang.  oh.  Look.
[Laughs] I have a
question for Greg.  This is where my older sister and I fell.
So, who will you help first?
Uh, I don't know.  Big sister is strong, so maybe
Chiko, Chiko is
strong.   It's
strong.  Well, the first thing you need to do to help me is to use your power,
since your snow power is weak.  This would be more helpful.
Yeah.  Oh, really?
[Music]
Where are you going? Did you go to the side?
Uh, that's quite a lot
.
Snowpo is better.
Snowboarding is faster.
Huh? I
thought we'd go a little further in.
Ah, it's me.
Oh, wow
, this is bad, this is bad.  If you get on the back like this,
yes.  Get on the
back here.
Oh, well, well, yes, yes, yes, yes.  Should I get off?
[music]
Yes.  You should get off.
yes.  wait a minute.
Oh, ugh.  Oh, that's scary.  This place is scary.
wait a minute.  This is scary.   Here we go
.
oh.  Safety, safety, and so on.   No
, it's fun.   It's
incredibly easy and fun, even if you can't ski.
yes.  Ithinkbetter.
Great success.
Great success.  Great success.  Great success.  Great success.
[Music]
With the snow monster was
time to head out to
final
destination located to the soul of the
volunasweand to
the of the mountain more the up me like it was real
[Music]
[Applause] You can't
see it anymore.  Wow.
yes.   thank you for your
hard work.   I'm looking forward to
dinner.   Let's go to a
hot spring.  tired.  sleepy.   Y-
yes.  That's a bit
expensive.   That's
amazing.  Look at this.  This has a hole in it.  It's hot.  Is there such a thing as mountain juice?
Mountain juice.  Okay.   It's warm
.  It's warm.  juice.
cheers.
[Music]
Cheers.  Like apple cider
but grape grape
[music]
cider before me looks it
uplet's see what the outside looks like oh there is the sauna can see it down there have now removal equipment just sitting around
because they
need how nice it is so nice
high Oh,
yes, the ceiling is high so it feels really spacious.
I guess I'm over
here, but now just
outside there is the same
.  Looks like a lot of them will come out.  looks delicious.   I'm going to gain weight
again.
Really?
Me too.
Cheers, cheers. It's strong, it's
really strong. Yeah,
which one should I eat first? Let's eat.
Yes.  like.  Smoked cheese.  This is a sake tasting set.   You can enjoy
four different types of alcohol.
[Music]
Delicious.  It's also easy to drink.  I'm saying the same thing again.  Beautiful.
delicious.
[Music] It's
delicious.  yes.  Shin-chan,
hurry up or I'm already super full.
Stop it, stop it.   A bowl of
miso soup helps reset your mind.
TRUE.  yes.  This is the last ice cream.  It will come.
Yeah.  fart.  It seems your mouth wasn't reset after all.
Stop it.
Yeah.   It means I'm too
full to walk.
[Music]
Yeah.  I'm happy.  oh.
oh.  Well, this is it.
Japan has already drawn the line.  I don't really understand it, even though it's not in Japan.  I can't come up with a comment right away.  yes.  While I was eating, Mr. Nakai came over and laid out the futon for me.  Like this.  It's absolutely perfect, isn't it?   That's why traditional Japanese
inns are so great.
[Music]
Okay, let's go for breakfast.
[Music] Let's
go.  Something's up, something's up.
[Music]
Jump
One more time, one more time.
[Music]
Red.  Ah, it's
okay.  What do you see? That's the other side.
mountain.  Oh, it's a mountain
[music]
? That's fine.  Is that okay
? It must have cracked under its own weight
.
Wow, that's amazing.  Three sheets, please.
[Applause] That's
really high.   That's
really high.  It's like we
need one of those elimination devices for every single crab.  Look.
One vehicle removed at a time.   It got
bent.  I did it.  yes.
yes.
yes.  yes.  Okay.  Spin.
yes.  wait a minute.
Yeah, that's pretty
cool.  I can see it.  Uh,
[music] I do that kind of thing
.
Upon closer
inspection, I
realized the skis were telemark skis, which
come in handy for back
country travel. It turns out that if you wanted to get closer in the winter, this was one of the only ways you could. The last measurement I saw for the snowfalls in this part of town showed that they were 5 meters or about 15 feet, which is why mechanized snow removal equipment is a necessary part of winter life at this resort.
Being cut off from here decided
to descend.
Huh? Where's Greg? Yes.
[Music]
Yeah.  ent.
Oh, a snow taxi.
[Music]
Yeah, I think Onnaori is really getting cooler and cooler, isn't she? It's amazing.  Oh, something's buried.  This isn't the
second
floor, is it?  I'll do it right away.
The wind was noisy, but the
only audio you missed was getting out by the
ladies walking on top of the building
. For a limited time
during winter, they
use this field for all sorts of winter
activities like
riding an incator and tubing only other
people in the
players. It's like
being
around
the area and getting some cool
shots,
traversing through the
roads with giant
snowwalls. I just
said that by mistake.
[Music]
[Music] I
thought I'd take over because I'm the one who's tired, but then this happened.  And
[music]
No, it's again.  Ah, I'm scared now.
[Music]
Yes,wereallydidend
updrivingback
throughfrom
FukushimatoYamagat
throughmountain
tunnelthatwasKlong.